{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 120,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "473 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "43 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2978 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "198 rem 8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9646 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "742 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6063 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "2021 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5400 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "600 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6722 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "480 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "722 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "144 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2377 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "216 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "322 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "46 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6836 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "488 rem 4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3206 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "229 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "660 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "66 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3878 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "277 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &#xF7; 7621",
      "answer": "0 rem 13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2336 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "389 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9807 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "1225 rem 7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1344 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "224 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5510 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "423 rem 11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3342 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1114 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "960 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "320 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9216 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "576 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3080 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "616 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9690 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "646 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1118 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "93 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "47 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "23 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1464 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "183 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9032 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "1129 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "732 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "122 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7768 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "971 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "8602 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "716 rem 10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4877 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "609 rem 5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6690 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "955 rem 5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9865 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "1644 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5709 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "519 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5208 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "434 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2370 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "237 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4501 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "900 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7512 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "626 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "1 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5652 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1884 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2103 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "701 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3202 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "1601 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1620 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "135 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2186 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "1093 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5622 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "937 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2626 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "202 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6170 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "3085 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3810 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "762 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1948 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "389 rem 3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &#xF7; 8632",
      "answer": "0 rem 15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "87 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "5 rem 7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1110 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "277 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "730 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "146 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1140 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "76 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3738 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "267 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2915 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "971 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2671 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "534 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "110 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "55 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4672 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "2336 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3825 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "255 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2714 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "678 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &#xF7; 6631",
      "answer": "0 rem 11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2955 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "591 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &#xF7; 7011",
      "answer": "0 rem 10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9986 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "832 rem 2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "93 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "23 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9086 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "649 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "563 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "80 rem 3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9020 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "820 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7112 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "1016 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6267 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "447 rem 9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3945 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "789 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6514 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "1302 rem 4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3676 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "919 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4971 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1657 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5547 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "369 rem 12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &#xF7; 4266",
      "answer": "0 rem 6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7691 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "854 rem 5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4001 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "500 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4039 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "673 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "8796 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "733 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4410 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1470 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7458 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "2486 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4875 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "325 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2735 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "547 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4680 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "520 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "364 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "28 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4048 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "368 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2873 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "221 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "8694 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "2898 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3432 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "1716 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9365 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "668 rem 13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3909 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1303 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3433 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "429 rem 1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7648 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "956 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7972 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "498 rem 4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9198 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "657 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3730 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "310 rem 10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7920 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "1320 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "860 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "86 rem 0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["qr"]
    }
  ]
}
